Hello world, this is Salma Shurrab. I live in Gaza and have been living in Gaza my whole life.
That means I've witnessed so many aggressions on Gaza, but yet have I ever seen anything this aggressive?
The aggression on Gaza have been going for the fifth day by now, and thankfully I still have my home and I still have my life and my family.
This time I'm doubting that I'll make it out alive. All my friends have either lost their house, a family member.
This time there's no safe place around. Yesterday we have to evacuate the whole building.
I have to leave my room, my house and my memories to go to a place that is no safer than my house.
So we had to return back home because if I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die in my house.
This is my bed. I've moved it several times this night trying to find the safest room to be with my family.
This is my bag ready to evacuate anytime with all the essentials I need.
I don't think it's enough for me to survive, but I'll try my best to stay alive and tell the truth.
Yesterday they have bombed the only borders we have with the world to get out of this war zone, but they're not letting us get out.
They're making us stuck in this cage and making everyone wait for their death.
Gaza is no longer a city to live in. It's a ghost town. All the places I work in is destroyed by now.
The university in my graduation year. I don't think I'll ever graduate by now.
There's no shelters. They cut off the water. All the bathrooms are closed.
They cut off the internet. They bombed all the internet places in Gaza.
So the internet connection is very poor and it's very bad. That means the truth is not coming out as it should be.
And I haven't slept in two days. Every time I close my eye, I either hear a bomb or see a light or hear a noise or hear a scream or hear a neighbor evacuating.
So I'm like, should I evacuate now or should I just wait for my death in my own house?
It's really confusing.
Here we're living times that have never existed in any humanity possible.
This aggression needs to be over.
Palestinian life matter. Gaza life matter. We're not numbers.